Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- China College Files, Series IV
  - Yenching University
    - Correspondence
      - Stelle, Bergen S., 1929 (Box 353, Folder 5429)
      - Stevens, Nellie H., 1928 (Box 353, Folder 5430)
      - Stewart, Maxwell S., 1926 (Box 353, Folder 5430)
      - Stock, Arthur J., 1923-1945 (Box 353, Folder 5431, 5432)
      - Stone, Editha, 1938 (Box 353, Folder 5433)
      - Stone, Hattie M. Foundation, 1928-1934 (Box 353, Folder 5433)
      - Strong, Walter A., 1931 (Box 353, Folder 5434)
      - Stryker, Alice J., 1924 (Box 353, Folder 5434)
      - Stuart, John Leighton, 1914-1922 (Box 353, Folder 5435-5447)
      - Stuart, John Leighton, 1923-1926 Sep (Box 354, Folder 5448-5464)
      - Stuart, John Leighton, 1926 Oct-1928 (Box 355, Folder 5465-5480)
      - Stuart, John Leighton, 1929-1931 Nov (Box 356, Folder 5481-5494)
      - Stuart, John Leighton, 1931 Dec-1934 Aug (Box 357, Folder 5495-5510)
      - Stuart, John Leighton, 1934 Sep-1937 Apr (Box 358, Folder 5511-5526)
      - Stuart, John Leighton, 1937 May-1939 (Box 359, Folder 5527-5540)
      - Stuart, John Leighton, 1940-1949,n.d. (Box 360, Folder 5541-5550)
      - Stuart, John L. (son of J. Leighton), 1942-1945 (Box 360, Folder 5551)
      - Stuart, Mary H., 1922-1925 (Box 360, Folder 5552)
      - Stuart, Warren H., 1937-1945 (Box 360, Folder 5553)
      - Stuckert, R.C., 1930-1931 (Box 360, Folder 5554)
      - Su, Chester, 1930-1933 (Box 360, Folder 5554)
      - The Sun, New York, 1928-1936 (Box 360, Folder 5555)
      - Sun Life Assurance Co. of Canada, 1938 (Box 360, Folder 5555)
      - Sweet, Lennig, 1931 (Box 360, Folder 5556)
      - Sweet, William E., 1922-1924 (Box 360, Folder 5556)
      - Swiss Committee for Yenching, 1928-1939 (Box 360, Folder 5557)
      - Tamblyn and Brown, 1928-1935 (Box 361, Folder 5558-5560)
      - Tan, C.C., 1934 (Box 361, Folder 5561)
      - Tan Pin-pin, 1940-1944 (Box 361, Folder 5561)
      - Tang, D.S., 1934 (Box 361, Folder 5561)
      - T'ang Ping-liang, 1941 (Box 361, Folder 5561)
      - Tasker, Ray C., 1924-1926 (Box 361, Folder 5562)
      - Tayler, J.B., 1922-1934 (Box 361, Folder 5563, 5564)
      - Taylor, George and Roberta, 1937-1943 (Box 361, Folder 5565)
      - Terman, E.L., 1922-1929 (Box 361, Folder 5566)
      - Tewksbury, Donald, 1921-1934 (Box 361, Folder 5567)
      - Thomas, Elbert D., 1934-1941 (Box 361, Folder 5567)
      - Thompson, Warren S. (See: Scripps Found. for Research in Population Problems) (Box 361, Folder 5567)
      - Thompson, William J. and Mary, 1924-1947 (Box 361, Folder 5568, 5569)
      - Thornburg, S.R., 1923-1936 (Box 361, Folder 5570)
      - Tien, Gerald, 1940-1942 (Box 361, Folder 5570)
      - Torii, R., 1939 (Box 361, Folder 5570)
      - Treat, Payson J. (See: Stanford University) (Box 361, Folder 5570)
      - Tsai, Stephen (See also: under Galt, Howard), 1931-1947 (Box 361, Folder 5571-5577)
      - Tsao, C.P., 1927 (Box 362, Folder 5578)
      - Tsung Wei-hsien, 1929-1930 (Box 362, Folder 5578)
      - Tsur, Y.T., 1932-1933 (Box 362, Folder 5578)
      - United Clearing Board, 1944-1945 (Box 362, Folder 5579)
      - United Committee for Christian Universities of China, 1931-1935 (Box 362, Folder 5579)
      - United Press Associations, 1924-1933 (Box 362, Folder 5580)
      - United States Department of Agriculture, 1930 (Box 362, Folder 5581)
      - United States Department of Commerce, 1922-1923 (Box 362, Folder 5581)
      - University of Southern California, 1920-1932 (Box 362, Folder 5582)
      - VanVoorhis, Linda Lyon, 1928-1946 (Box 362, Folder 5583)
      - Veghte, Adeline H., 1929-1939 (Box 362, Folder 5584)
      - Vincent, Howell and Agnes and William, 1920-1946 (Box 362, Folder 5585)
      - Wagner, Augusta, 1927-1945 (Box 362, Folder 5586)
      - Waller, Margaret Louise, 1931 (Box 362, Folder 5587)
      - Wallis, Allan D., 1925-1930 (Box 362, Folder 5588)
      - Walton, W.E., 1924-1927 (Box 362, Folder 5589)
      - Wang Chih-yi, 1941 (Box 362, Folder 5589)
      - Wang Jun-chuan and Chen Chi-lan, 1939-1944 (Box 362, Folder 5589)
      - Wang, K.P., 1939 (Box 362, Folder 5590)
      - Wang Kung-chih, 1944 (Box 362, Folder 5590)
      - Wang Sui, 1924-1930 (Box 362, Folder 5590)
      - Ward, Ralph and Mildred, 1927-1928 (Box 362, Folder 5591)
      - Warner, Frank B., 1920 (Box 362, Folder 5591)
      - Warner, Franklin H., 1922-1945 (Box 362, Folder 5592-5596)
      - Warner, Gertrude Bass, 1927-1940 (Box 363, Folder 5597)
      - Warner, Langdon, 1932-1936 (Box 363, Folder 5597)
      - Washburn, Mr. and Mrs. William Ives, 1924-1936 (Box 363, Folder 5598)
      - Warnshuis, Abbe L., 1930-1936 (Box 363, Folder 5599)
      - re. Water tower pagoda, 1925-1930 (Box 363, Folder 5600)
      - Webber, Hattie L., 1935-1936 (Box 363, Folder 5601)
      - Webster, E.S., 1930-1937 (Box 363, Folder 5601)
      - Webster, M. Shannon, 1923-1924 (Box 363, Folder 5601)
      - Wee, K.A., 1923-1941 (Box 363, Folder 5602, 5603)
      - Wei Wen-yuan, 1942 (Box 363, Folder 5604)
      - Wei Yung-ch'ing, 1940-1944 (Box 363, Folder 5605-5607)
      - Weigle, Luther A., 1935 (Box 363, Folder 5608)
      - Welch, Edgar T., 1937-1939 (Box 363, Folder 5608)
      - Weyerhauser family, 1923-1942 (Box 363, Folder 5609)
      - Wheaton College YMCA (Norton, MA), 1930-1948 (Box 363, Folder 5610)
      - re. Wheeler Memorial Chapel, 1921-1935 (Box 363, Folder 5611)
      - Wheeler, W. Reginald, 1919-1945 (Box 363, Folder 5612-5614)
      - White, Roberta, 1922-1933 (Box 364, Folder 5615)
      - Whittelsey, Delia Y., 1943-1944 (Box 364, Folder 5616)
      - Wiant, Bliss and Mildred, 1922-1948 (Box 364, Folder 5617-5623)
      - Wick, Myron C., Jr. and Frances, 1921-1938 (Box 364, Folder 5624)
      - Williams, Anna P., 1928-1936 (Box 364, Folder 5625)
      - Williams, Jesse Feiring, 1931-1939 (Box 364, Folder 5625)
      - Williams, Walter and Sara, 1924-1944 (Box 364, Folder 5626, 5627)
      - Williamson, Nina, 1929-1935 (Box 364, Folder 5628, 5629)
      - Wilson, Amy L., 1933 (Box 365, Folder 5630)
      - Wilson, Earl O., 1919-1944 (Box 365, Folder 5631-5634)
      - Wilson, Stanley D. and Anna Lane, 1921-1945 (Box 365, Folder 5635-5640)
      - Winters, Ernest C., 1924-1937 (Box 365, Folder 5641)
      - Wolferz, Louis and Katherine, 1917-1944 (Box 365, Folder 5642)
      - Women's Union Christian Colleges in the Orient, Joint Committee of, 1919-1928 (Box 365, Folder 5643, 5644)
      - Woo, H.F., 1927-1931 (Box 366, Folder 5645)
      - Wood, Mabel A., 1936 (Box 366, Folder 5646)
      - Wood, Myfanwy, 1928-1935 (Box 366, Folder 5646)
      - Wooley, Mary E., 1922-1940 (Box 366, Folder 5647)
      - Woolverton, Samuel, 1923-1948 (Box 366, Folder 5648)
      - Woon, C.F., 1923-1929 (Box 366, Folder 5649)
      - Wright, William Burnet, Jr., 1921-1940 (Box 366, Folder 5649)
      - Wu Chenfu (Francis), 1932-1945 (Box 366, Folder 5650-5652)
      - Wu, Chi-Yu, 1931-1945 (Box 366, Folder 5652)
      - Wu, George K.T., 1933 (Box 366, Folder 5653)
      - Wu Kei-chuan, 1926-1931 (Box 366, Folder 5653)
      - Wu, W.T., 1936 (Box 366, Folder 5653)
      - Wu Yu-chen, 1934-1936 (Box 366, Folder 5653)
      - Yang, C.K., 1939-1940 (Box 366, Folder 5654)
      - Yang, David K., 1928 (Box 366, Folder 5654)
      - Yang Ming-hsien, 1944 (Box 366, Folder 5654)
      - Yang Sheng-mao, 1943 (Box 366, Folder 5654)
      - Yee, Samuel L., 1929-1930 (Box 366, Folder 5655)
      - Yen, W.W., 1932 (Box 366, Folder 5655)
      - Yenta Christian Fellowship, 1926-1938 (Box 366, Folder 5656)
      - Young, Ruth C., 1938-1940 (Box 366, Folder 5657)
      - Yu Hung-ao, 1940-1941 (Box 366, Folder 5657)
      - Yu Yu-mei, 1944 (Box 366, Folder 5658)
      - Yuan Grace, 1937 (Box 366, Folder 5658)
      - Yuki, Anthony Toshimichi (Lee, Anthony), 1935-1936 (Box 366, Folder 5658)
    - Financial records
      - Ledgers: Yenching University (2 vol.), 1921-1956 (Box 367, Folder 5659, 5660)
      - Ledger: Yenching College for Women, 1946-1957 (Box 368, Folder 5661)
      - Transfer book: Yenching University (See: oversize material), 1929-1949 (Box 368, Folder 5662)
      - Transfer book: Yenching college for Women, 1929-1946 (Box 368, Folder 5663)
      - Register of Trust Funds (Box 369, Folder 5664)
      - Register of Trust Funds, ca. 1933 (Box 369, Folder 5665)
      - re. McBrier Foundation, 1930-1952,n.d. (Box 369, Folder 5666-5668)
      - Pledge card samples, 1930-1944 (Box 369, Folder 5669)
      - re. Student Loan Fund, 1931-1941 (Box 369, Folder 5670)
      - Miscellaneous, 1920-1949,n.d. (Box 369, Folder 5671, 5672)
    - Periodical publications
      - Arts and Letters News, 1941 (Box 370, Folder 5673)
      - College of Public Affairs: Public Affairs, 1934, 1935 (Box 370, Folder 5674)
      - College of Public Affairs: Quarterly News, 1935-1937 (Box 370, Folder 5674)
      - College of Public Affairs: News Bulletin, 1937-1940 (Box 370, Folder 5674)
      - Faculty Bulletin, 1928-1946 (Box 370, Folder 5675-5687)
      - The New Mandarin (School of Chinese Studies), 1926 (Box 370, Folder 5687A)
      - Peking News, 1921-1930 (Box 371, Folder 5688, 5689)
      - Peking University Magazine, 1919-1920 (Box 371, Folder 5690)
      - Science Notes, 1934-1941, 1947 (Box 371, Folder 5691)
      - Sociology Fellowship News, 1930 (Box 371, Folder 5692)
      - Truth and Life, 1930 (Box 371, Folder 5693)
      - Yearbook ( The Yenchinian), 1928, 1929 (Box 371, Folder 5694)
      - Yearbook ( The Yenchinian ), 1938, 1940, 1941,n.d. (Box 372, Folder 5695)
      - Yenching Gazette, 1932 (Box 372, Folder 5696A)
      - Yenching Fortnightly, 1945 Nov-1946 Jan (Box 372, Folder 5696)
      - The Yenching Index Numbers, 1940 (Box 372, Folder 5697)
      - The Yenching Index Numbers, 1941, 1947-1948 (Box 373, Folder 5698, 5699)
      - Yenching Journal of Chinese Studies, 1927-1929 (Box 373, Folder 5700-5702)
      - Yenching News (China edition), 1935-1937 (Box 373, Folder 5703, 5704)
      - Yenching News (China edition), 1938-1939, 1940-1941, 1943-1945 (Box 374, Folder 5705,5705A, 5706)
      - Yenching News (U.S. edition), 1931-1950 (Box 374, Folder 5707-5709)
      - Yenta Journalism News, 1934 (Box 374, Folder 5710)
      - Miscellaneous, 1926-1945 (Box 374, Folder 5711)
    - Publicity/reports
      - For material related to: Harvard-Yenching Institute, Princeton-Yenching Foundation, Wellesley-Yenching, see Series VI, Related Organizations
      - Brochures, pamphlets re. the University, 1918-1949,n.d. (Box 375, Folder 5712-5718)
      - Brochures, pamphlets re. Yenching College for Women (and its predecessor, North China Union Women's College), 1912-1925 (Box 376, Folder 5719)
      - Brochures, pamphlets re. Yenching College for Women, 1926-1942,n.d. (Box 376, Folder 5720)
      - Historical statements, memoranda, 1892-1949,n.d. (Box 376, Folder 5721-5727)
      - Newsletters, news releases, 1927-1953,n.d. (Box 377, Folder 5728-5738)
      - Newspaper and magazine articles, 1929 (Box 377, Folder 5739)
      - Newspaper and magazine articles, 1930-1949,n.d. (Box 378, Folder 5740, 5741)
      - Promotional Committee activities, 1929-1936 (Box 378, Folder 5742)
      - Testimonials for publicity purposes, arranged alphabetically, 1920-1936 (Box 378, Folder 5743)
      - Material related to Dwight W. Edwards monograph on Yenching, 1952-1960 (Box 378, Folder 5744)
- Audio-Visual Materials, Series V
  A searchable database of many photographs contained in Series V is available.
  The materials in Series V have been divided according to format:
  1) Films, filmstrips
  2) Photographs
  3) Slides
  4) Sketches
  5) Sound recordings
  General films about United Board work in China and geographical areas of China are followed by films related to specific educational institutions in Asia. Film titles are provided as available. A small number of filmstrips follow the films.
  Photographs are organized in the following sequence:
  a) Associated Boards and United Board activities in the United States
  b) China Colleges
  c) Other educational institutions in Asia
  d) Organizations related to the China Colleges
  e) Miscellaneous photographs of China and Korea
  The organization within these categories varies according to the number, size and subject matter of photographs available.
  The slides include glass lantern slides and more modern varieties. Slides relating to four China Colleges are followed by a number of boxes of unidentified slides.
  The sketches are by Mary V. Thayer of Ginling College.
  The sound recordings consist of two phonograph records and seventeen soundscript discs.
  - Films, Filmstrips
    Films on DVDs are also available as digital files on the repository server.
    - General Films
      - "China Looks Ahead" (6 reels) (Box 379, Folder 5745)
      - "China Looks Ahead" (VHS - 3 tapes, numbered 1,2,4) (Box 463)
      - "China Looks Ahead" (3 DVDs) (numbered 1,2,4) (Box 466)
      - "Front Line of Democracy: (1 reel) (Box OV11-B3)
      - "Front Line of Democracy" (VHS tape), 1949 (Box 464)
      - "Front Line of Democracy" (DVD), 1949 (Box 466)
      - "Domke film on West China" (Box 380, Folder 5746)
      - "Domke film on West China" (DVD) (Box 466)
      - "Salt Wells" (Box 380, Folder 5746)
      - "Salt Wells" (DVD) (Box 466)
      - "Yunkang Caves" (Box 380, Folder 5746)
      - "Yunkang Caves" (DVD) (Box 466)
      - "China's Gifts to the West" (2 reels); Shadow Shows (Box 380, Folder 5746)
      - "China's Gifts to the West" (DVDs); Shadow Shows (DVD) (Box 466)
    - Fukien Christian University
      - "A Visit to Fukien Christian University" (1 reel) (Box 381, Folder 5747)
      - "A Visit to Fukien Christian University" (VHS - 2 tapes) (Box 464)
      - "A Visit to Fukien Christian University" (DVDs) (Box 466)
      - "Chinese Village Life Near Fukien Christian University" (3 reels) (Box 381, Folder 5747)
      - "Chinese Village Life Near Fukien Christian University" (VHS tape) (Box 463)
    - Ginling College
      - "It Happened at Ginling" (3 reels) (Box 382, Folder 5748)
      - "It Happened at Ginling" (VHS - 4 tapes) (Box 463)
      - "It Happened at Ginling" (Box 466)
      - "Copy of Lady Hosie's Film" (Box 383, Folder 5749)
      - "Copy of Lady Hosie's Film" (DVD) (Box 466)
      - "Glimpses of Ginling College - Captions and Comments": typed script relating to the "cutting of 484 feet from 1200 ft story film 'It Happened at Ginling' (Box 383, Folder 5749)
      - re. Poultry experiment (Box 383, Folder 5749)
      - re. Poultry experiment (DVD) (Box 466)
      - "The War-Time Service of a Christian College" (Box 383, Folder 5749)
      - "The War-Time Service of a Christian College" (VHS tape) (Box 463)
      - "The War-Time Service of a Christian College" (DVD) (Box 466)
      - "Ginling College" (Box 384, Folder 5750)
      - "Ginling College" (VHS tape) (Box 463)
      - "Ginling College" (DVD) (Box 466)
      - "Undaunted, Ginling Educates China's Women" (1 reel) (Box 384, Folder 5750)
      - "Undaunted, Ginling Educates China's Women" (VHS tape) (Box 463)
      - "Undaunted, Ginling Educates China's Women" (DVD) (Box 466)
    - Lingnan University
      - Untitled film (Box 384, Folder 5751)
    - Nanking, University of
      - Re. University of Nanking, incl. re. Sericulture (4 reels) (Box 385, Folder 5752)
      - Re. University of Nanking, incl. re. Sericulture (VHS - 4 tapes) (Box 464)
      - Re. University of Nanking, incl. re. Sericulture (DVDs) (Box 466)
      - "A Christian University in the Capital of China" and film on weaving (7 reels) (Box 386, Folder 5753)
      - "A Christian University in the Capital of China" (VHS - 6 tapes) (Box 464)
      - "A Christian University in the Capital of China" (DVDs) (Box 466)
    - Shantung Christian University/Cheeloo University
      - "Cheeloo Hospital film by Dr. Anna Scott" (1 reel) (Box 386, Folder 5754)
      - "Cheeloo Hospital film by Dr. Anna Scott" (VHS tape) (Box 463)
      - "Cheeloo Hospital film by Dr. Anna Scott" (DVD) (Box 466)
    - West China Union University
      - Untitled film re. WCUU (2 reels) (Box 386, Folder 5755)
      - Untitled film re. WCUU (2 VHS tape) (Box 465)
    - Yenching University
      - "Old Yenching film" (1 reel) (Box 387, Folder 5756)
      - "Old Yenching film" (VHS tape) (Box 465)
      - "Old Yenching film" (included on DVD) (Box 466)
      - "The Treasure of Shu Ch'un Yuan" (3 reels) (second copy in Oversize material) (Box 387, Folder 5756)
      - "The Treasure of Shu Ch'un Yuan" (VHS - 3 tapes) (Box 465)
      - "The Treasure of Shu Ch'un Yuan" (included on DVD) (Box 466)
      - Untitled films (3 reels) (Box 387, Folder 5756)
      - Untitled films (VHS - 3 tapes) (Box 465)
      - Untitled films (included on DVD) (Box 466)
      - "Unused editings from Yenching film" (5 reels) (Box 388, Folder 5757)
      - "Unused editings from Yenching film" (included on DVD) (Box 466)
      - Film edited out of "Yenching movie" (Box 388, Folder 5757)
      - Film edited out of "Yenching movie" (included on DVD) (Box 466)
      - Commencement Procession Led by Dr. Francis Chen (1 reel) (Box 388, Folder 5757)
      - Commencement Procession Led by Dr. Francis Chen (VHS tape) (Box 465)
      - Commencement Procession Led by Dr. Francis Chen (included on DVD) (Box 466)
    - Chosen Christian University
      - Untitled film (Box 389, Folder 5758)
      - Untitled film (included on DVD) (Box 466)
    - Tunghai University
      - "Tunghai Today" (Box 389, Folder 5759)
      - "Tunghai Today" (DVD) (Box 466)
    - Yonsei University
      - "Yonsei University" (Box 389, Folder 5760)
      - "Yonsei University" (included on DVD) (Box 466)
    - Miscellaneous films about educational institutions
      - "Underwood films re. Korea, CCU and Severance" (5 reels) (Box 389, Folder 5761)
      - Severance, Chosen Christian College, Yonsei (VHS tape) (Box 463)
      - "Education in China" (Box 389, Folder 5761)
      - Federated University Film (Box 389, Folder 5761)
      - 8 unidentified reels (Box 390, Folder 5762)
      - 7 unidentified reels (Box 391, Folder 5763)
        3 films are of campus scenes at Soochow University, 1 film is outtakes from "Frontline of Democracy" 1 film is a home movie of a picnic, possibly on West Lake, Hangchow
    - Miscellaneous filmstrips
      - "Four Chinese Women -- New Horizons" (Box 392, Folder 5764)
      - "March of Missions" (Box 392, Folder 5764)
      - Re. Shantung/Cheeloo (Box 392, Folder 5764)
      - Re. West China (Box 392, Folder 5764)
      - "Korea 2333 B.C. - 1951 A.D." (Box 392, Folder 5764)
      - "The Voice of Prayer is Never Silent" (Box 392, Folder 5764)
      - "The University of Tomorrow" (Box 392, Folder 5764)
      - "While Earth Rolls Onward Into Light" (Box 392, Folder 5764)
      - 4 unidentified strips (Box 392, Folder 5764)
    - Other Untitled Films
      - First frames show:Student Life (6 reels) (Box OV11-B1)
      - First frames show: Landscape (3 reels, one may be Sikang) (Box OV11-B1)
      - People (2 reels) (Box OV11-B1)
      - Chinese Opera (1 reel) (Box OV11-B2)
      - Chinese film (Box OV11-B2)
  - Photographs
    - Associated Boards for Christian Colleges in China
      - Conferences and dinners, 1935-1937 (Box OVd7)
      - Conferences and dinners, 1938-1940, n.d. (Box 394, Folder 5766)
    - United Board for Christian Colleges in China
      - U.S. Chinese Student and Alumni Services, 1952-1955, n.d. (Box 394, Folder 5767)
      - Related individuals and groups (Box 394, Folder 5768)
    - Fukien Christian University
      - Buildings and scenes, 1937-1938, n.d. (Box 395)
      - Student activities, 1935-1948, n.d. (Box 395)
      - Agriculture, 1937, n.d. (Box 395)
      - Rural Service Center, 1934-1936, n.d. (Box 395)
      - Twenty-fifth anniversary, 1941 (Box 395)
      - Shaowu campus, 1938-1946 (Box 395)
      - Postwar, 1946,n.d. (Box 395)
      - Students and alumni, 1927-1968, n.d. (Box 395)
      - Faculty and administrators (alphabetically) (Box 395)
      - Buildings and scenes, ca. 1920, 1946, n.d. (Box 396, Folder 5769-5770)
      - Faculty and administrators (alphabetically) (Box 396, Folder 5771)
      - Students and alumni, 1919-1958, n.d. (Box 396, Folder 5772)
      - Sung dynasty gravesite on Shaowu campus, 1939-1941 (Box 396, Folder 5773)
      - Vol. 1: Misc. early photos (Box 396, Folder 5774)
      - Vol. II: Re. visits to pottery villages, 1935 (Box 396, Folder 5775)
      - Vol. II: Miscellaneous (Box 393, Folder 5775a-h)
    - Ginling College
      - Old Ginling, 1916-pre 1923, n.d. (Box 397)
      - Constructing campus, 1920's, 1930's (Box 397)
      - Misc. photos, Nanking, 1920's-1937, n.d. (Box 397)
      - Trek to the West, 1937-1938 (Box 397)
      - Ginling in Nanking, 1938-1939 (Box 397)
      - Ginling in Chengtu, 1940-1946 (Box 397)
      - Return to Nanking and war damage to campus, 1946-1947, n.d. (Box 397)
      - Postwar, 1946-1948 (Box 397)
      - Rural Service Station, 1947-1948 (Box 397)
      - Alumnae (alphabetically) (Box 398)
      - Faculty and administrators (alphabetically) (Box 398)
      - Buildings and scenes, 1920's-1937, n.d. (Box 398)
      - President Wu Yi-fang, 1928-1948, n.d. (Box 398)
      - Miscellaneous, 1920s-1940s (Box 399)
      - Old Ginling, 1919-1921,n.d. (Box 400A, Folder 5777)
      - Dance dramas, 1935, 1937 (Box 400A, Folder 5777)
      - Trek to the West, 1938 (Box 400A, Folder 5778)
      - Ginling in Nanking, 1939 (Box 400A, Folder 5778)
      - Ginling in Chengtu (Box 400A, Folder 5779, 5780)
      - Ginling in Chengtu: Jenshow, Ginling's rural project (Box 400A, Folder 5781)
      - Return to Nanking (Box 400A, Folder 5781)
      - War damage (Box 400A, Folder 5782)
      - Postwar (Box 400A, Folder 5783)
      - Buildings and campus scenes (Box 400B, Folder 5784)
      - Faculty (Box 400B, Folder 5785)
      - Wu Yi-fang, President (Box 400B, Folder 5786)
      - Miscellaneous, 1923-1958,n.d. (Box 400B, Folder 5787-5791)
      - Negatives, misc. (Box 400B, Folder 5792)
      - Vol. I: Old Ginling (Box 401, Folder 5793)
      - Vol. II: Miscellaneous, ca.1920-1926 (Box 401, Folder 5794)
      - Vol. III: Miscellaneous (See Oversize material)
    - Hangchow Christian College (University)
      - Buildings and scenes, 1948,n.d. (Box 402, Folder 5795)
      - Scenes of student life: classes, 1917,n.d. (Box 402, Folder 5796)
      - Scenes of student life: dormitories, n.d. (Box 402, Folder 5797)
      - Scenes of student life: miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 402, Folder 5798)
      - Scenes of student life: library, n.d. (Box 402, Folder 5799)
      - Student, faculty and alumni groups and portraits, 1917-1950,n.d. (Box 402, Folder 5800)
      - Photos and commentary by Clarence B. Day, 1950-1951,n.d. (Box 402, Folder 5801)
      - Oversize photograph
    - Huachung (college) University
      - Buildings and scenes, 1936, 1941, 1945 (Box 403, Folder 5802, 5803)
      - Faculty, administrators and students, 1931-1948,n.d. (Box 403, Folder 5804)
      - Huachung University monograph: cuts (Box 403, Folder 5805)
      - Buildings and scenes, 1936, 1941, 1945 (Box 403, Folder 5802, 5803)
      - Faculty, administrators and students, 1931-1948,n.d. (Box 403, Folder 5804)
      - Huachung University monograph: cuts (Box 403, Folder 5805)
    - Hwa Nan College
      - Buildings and scenes (Box 404, Folder 5806)
      - Faculty, administrators and alumnae, 1938-1943,n.d. (Box 404, Folder 5807)
      - Student life, 1938-1943,n.d. (Box 404, Folder 5808)
      - "Hwa Nan College at Nanping" (compilation), 1938-1946 (Box 404, Folder 5809)
    - Lingnan University
      - Buildings and scenes: Agricultural Hall (Box 405, Folder 5800A)
      - Buildings and scenes: Grant Hall, 1918, 1932,n.d. (Box 405, Folder 5801A)